Waiting for Anya is a drama, war film directed by Ben Cookson.
During the harrows of WWII, Jo, a young shepherd along with the help of the widow Horcada, helps
to smuggle Jewish children across the border from southern France into Spain.
Jo, played by Noah Schnapp.
Korporal, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Benjamin, played by Frederick Schmidt.
Leutnant, played by Tómas Lemarquis.
Papa, played by Gilles Marini.
Maman, played by Elsa Zylberstein.
Waiting for Anya is a 2020 historical war drama film
co-written and directed by Ben Cookson.
It is a film adaptation of the 1990 novel of the same name by Michael Morpurgo.
The film stars Noah Schnapp, Thomas Kretschmann, Frederick
Schmidt, Jean Reno, and Anjelica Huston.
The film premiered at the 2020 Miami Jewish Film
Festival and was released on 7 February 2020.
The tone is emotional.